Guide to the General Subjects Photography Collection
California Historical Society
- Photographers
  - San Francisco
    - Williams Norton (W. I. Williams and E. Norton)
    - Wilton, Thomas H.
    - Winberg, John Albert
    - Wise, James
    - Wise Prindle (James and Benjamin Augustus)
    - Wolfenstein, Valentin
    - Woods, David Holmes
    - Worden, Willard E.
    - Worthington, William Thomas
  - San Jose
    - Button Higgins
    - California Art Company (J.A. Harliss and J.O. Valpey)
    - Carruthers (William, John, or Katherine)
    - Clayton, James Atkins
    - Haussler, P.
    - Heering, John H.
    - Henfield's New Gallery
    - Hill Watkins
    - Pomeroy, Edward
    - Souvenir Photographic Studio (Loryea Bros., Loryea Macaulay)
    - White Hubbel
    - White, George R.
    - Wright, Wilbur W.--#1,2
  - Santa Barbara
    - Newton, W.L.
  - Santa Cruz
    - Aichberg, Christian
    - Baldwin, John E.D.
    - Butler, Edward P.
    - Hodson, John R.
    - McKean Ort
  - Santa Rosa
    - Downing, Rea Rauscher
    - Miltz Swart (Theodore G. and John H.)
    - Piggott, James K.
    - Rendall, Stephen Arnold
    - Shaw, William
    - Watson, A.R.
  - Sonora
    - Wells
  - Stockton
    - Elliott, Orman
    - Higgins Photographic Gallery
    - Monaco
    - Reed, John Quincy
    - Spooner, John Pitcher
    - Stuart, William McCorsin
  - Ukiah
    - Carpenter, Aurelius Ormando
    - Saunders
  - Vallejo
    - Smith, James Girard
  - Watsonville
    - Clark, E.L.
  - Woodland
    - Davidson
    - Mitchell, W.H.
    - Rue, Lewis M.
  - Yreka
    - Heller, Louis
- Photography
  - General
  - Equipment
- Police
- Recreation
  - General
  - Amusement Parks
  - Archery
  - Auto Racing
  - Banquets
    - General
    - (1910-1919)
    - (1940-1949)
  - Baseball
    - Ante 1920
    - General--#1,2,3,4,5,6
  - Basketball
  - Billiards
  - Boating
  - Bocci Ball
  - Bowling
  - Boxing
  - Bull and Bear Fighting
  - Camping
    - General
    - (1880-1889)
    - (1900s)
  - Card Games--(1890-1899)
  - Circuses
  - Croquet
  - Cycling
    - Large Photos--#1,2
    - Small Photos
  - Dance
    - General
    - Ballet
      - General
      - Costume
      - Portraits
        - General--#1,2
        - Female
        - Male
      - Productions
    - Folk Dance
    - Interpretive
  - Diving
  - Dog Sledding
  - Fencing
  - Fishing
    - California Anglers Association
  - Football
  - Gambling
  - Golf--#1,2,3
  - Gymnastics
  - Horseracing
    - General
    - Trotting
  - Hunting
    - General
    - Toyon Duck Club
  - Ice Hockey
  - Ice Skating--#1,2
  - Log Rolling
  - Martial Arts
  - Olympic Games
  - Parades
    - General
    - Rose Bowl Parade
  - Parties
  - Picnics
  - Polo
  - Proms
  - Riding
  - Roller Skating
  - Rugby
  - Sculling
  - Shooting
  - Skiing
  - Skin Diving
  - Sledding
  - Soccer
  - Surfing
  - Swimming
    - General--#1,2
    - Ante 1930
    - Diving
  - Tennis--#1,2
  - Track and Field
  - Water Skiing
  - Weight Lifting
  - Wrestling
- Religion
  - General
  - Church of Jesus Christ and the Latter Day Saints
  - Roman Catholic--#1,2
  - Society of Friends
- Saddles
- Schools
- Science
  - General
  - Astronomy
  - Rockets--#1,2
- Social Groups
  - General
  - African-Americans
    - Civil Rights Movement
  - Austrians
  - Chinese
    - Large Photos
    - Photocopies
    - Small Photos
  - Dutch
  - English
  - Filipinos
  - French
  - Gays/Lesbians
  - Germans
  - Gypsies
  - Hippies
  - Hispanic-Americans
    - Large Photos--#1,2,3,4
    - Small Photos
  - Indigenous Americans (Indians)
    - General
      - Photocopies
      - Antiquities
      - Architecture
      - Arts and Crafts
        - Large Photos
        - Small Photos--#1,2
      - Ceremonies
      - Demonstrations
      - Expeditions, Early Contacts
    - Modoc War
    - Photographers
      - Crockwell, J.H.
      - Frothingham, Robert
      - Nicholson, Grace
    - Popular Depictions
    - Post-1950 Images
    - Reproductions of Paintings
    - Shasta County
    - Yosemite County
    - Yuma
  - Irish
  - Italian
  - Japanese
    - General
      - Large Photos--#1,2
      - Small Photos
    - Art
    - Expositions
    - Military
    - Theatre
  - Jewish
  - Nudists
  - Samoans
  - Scottish
  - Transvestites
  - Women
    - General
      - Large Photos--#1,2,3
      - Small Photos
    - Beauty Contests
    - Liberation
    - Organizations
    - Suffrage
- Theatre
  - General
  - (1860-1869)
  - (1870-1879)
  - (1890-1899)
  - Amateur
  - Burlesque
  - Female Impersonation
  - Magic
  - Mime
  - Minstrels
- Toys
  - Large Photos
  - Small Photos
  - San Francisco Chronicle Photos
- Transportation
  - Air
    - General--#1,2,3,4
    - Accidents
    - Balloon
    - Dirigibles
    - Exhibitions
    - Gliders
    - Helicopters
    - Personnel--#1,2
    - Schools--#1,2
  - Automotive
    - General--#1,2,3
    - (1900-1909)
    - (1910-1919)
    - (1920-1929)
    - (1930-1939)
    - (1960-1969)
    - Accidents
    - Dealers
    - Highways
      - General
      - Redwood Highway
    - Motorcycles
    - Parts and Service
    - Racing
    - Commercial
      - General--#1,2,3,4
      - Accidents
      - Design
      - Facilities
      - Interiors
      - Parts and Service
      - Personnel
      - Another Auto Transit Company
      - Auto Interurban Lines
      - B and H.T. Company
      - Borderland Transit Company
      - California Transit Company
      - Crown Stage Short Lines
      - Dunkirk Cab
      - Greyhound
        - Pacific Greyhound
        - Portland, OR
      - Los Angeles Motor Bus Company
      - Los Angeles Motor Coach Company
      - Los Angeles Railway
      - Motor Transit Company
      - Pacific Electric
      - Pickwick Stages
      - Safety Service Transportation Company
      - Stimson Transportation Company
      - Valley Transit Company
  - Draft
    - General
    - Carriages
    - Covered Wagons
    - Express Companies
      - General
      - Wells Fargo and Company
    - Pony Express
    - Stagecoaches
  - Rail
    - General--#1,2,3,4,5,6,7
    - Accidents
    - Construction
    - Electric
    - Ferries
    - Ocean Shore Railroad, Santa Cruz
    - Southern Pacific Railroad
  - Water
    - General
      - Barkentines
      - Barks
      - Battleships
      - Canoes
      - Cargo Ships
      - Container Ships
      - Deck Views
      - Drawings, Models
      - Ferries
      - Fishing Boats
      - Government Vessels
      - Interiors
      - Motor Boats
      - Ocean Liners
      - Paddle Wheels
      - Schooners
      - Ships (For identified ships see GS--Transportation--Water--Ships--Names)
      - Shipyards
      - Steam-Sails
      - Steamboats
      - Submarines
      - Yachts--#1,2
      - Miscellaneous
    - Ships
      - Names
        - (AA-AL)
        - (AM-AS)
        - (AT-AZ)
        - (CA-CH)
        - (CI-COK)
        - (COL-CZ)
        - (D)
        - (E)
        - (F)
        - (G)
        - (H)
        - (I-J)
        - (K)
        - (L)
        - (M)
        - (N)
        - (O)
        - (Ohioan)
        - (PA-PH)
        - (PI-PO)
        - (PR-PZ)
        - (Q-R)
        - (SA)
        - (SB-SO)
        - (SP-SZ)
        - (T)
        - (U-V)
        - (W)
        - (X-Z)
- U.S. Government
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA)
  - U.S. Postal Service (Post Office)
- U.S. History--War
  - Civil War
    - (California Hundred)
  - Indian Wars
  - Korean War
  - Mexican-American War
  - Spanish-American War
  - Vietnam War
    - Demonstrations
      - General
      - Berkeley to Oakland March (October 15-16, 1965)
      - Oakland Army Terminal (1965)
  - World War I
  - World War II
- U.S. Military
  - General
  - Air Force--#1,2
  - Army
    - Pre-1920
    - 1920-1959
    - 1960-1969
    - Army Corps of Engineers
  - Coast Guard
  - Marine Corps
  - National Guard
  - Navy
    - Ante 1920
    - (1920-1949)
    - (1950-1959)
    - (1960-1969)--#1,2
    - Great White Fleet (see: SF--U.S.--Navy--Great White Fleet)
    - Sea Lab
  - Organizations--USO
- Oversize Photographs, General Subjects
  - (A)
  - (B-D)
  - (E-H)
  - (I-O)
  - (P-S)
  - (T-Z)
  - Photographers
  - Ships
    - (A_N)
    - (O-Z)
  - Yosemite Valley--#1,2